http://www.ajsgems.com/privacy-policy

Security & Privacy at AJS Gems
Skip to main content
AJS Gems
Home Shop GemsAJS QualityGemstone ListBirthstonesGems by ColorGems by PriceHelpPaymentShippingReturn PolicyPrivacy PolicyGift CertificateFrequently Asked QuestionsCustomer ReviewsEducationClarity GradesGemstone HardnessGemstone ArticlesRefractive Index ChartGemstone ReferenceInvesting in GemstonesJewelry GalleryGemstone Setting IdeasAbout UsAbout AJS GemsAbout Arnold SilverbergContact UsGem CertsLogin AcctLoginManage Account
Security & Privacy
We Respect and Protect Your Privacy
At AJS Gems we are committed to protecting your privacy.  To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.
During online ordering a user must give certain contact information, we do not sell or use your personal information for anything other than transactions within our company:
Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers.
Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line, or from our shipper regarding delivery of your order.
In order to use this website, visitors and/or members are not required to complete any form or give us any information. All forms are optional. Giving additional information helps provide a more personalized experience on our site, but is not required.
In order to provide a personalized shopping experience at AJS Gems, we do use and collect cookies.  Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide features and to store items in your shopping cart. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. You will need to accept cookies in order to use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them.
Read our detailed Website Users Privacy Policy compliant with the new EU GPDR regulations
We use the information we collect about you only to process orders and to provide you with a pleasant seamless shopping experience.
Safe Technology
AJS Gems uses SSL encryption to process credit card payments.
All of your personal information is encrypted, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels across the Internet.
Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. We do not store customer credit card information on our servers.
Conflict Resolution
We are committed to resolving disputes within 24-48 hours. If a problem arises with an order or any other transaction users may contact us via phone, email or fax and we will respond within 24 hours.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via phone, email, or fax.
Phone: (662) 237-8353 Fax: (662) 237-8354 Email: customerservice@ajsgems.com
25% off on All Gems Under $500
Offer ends October 31stDiscount code:  OCT-25
Shopping Cart
There are no products in your shopping cart.0 Items | Total: $0.00
AJS Gems Newsletter
Read our latest newsletter Subscribe and be the first to know about news and future specials
E-mail *
Help
Payment Shipping Return PolicyCustomer Reviews Security & Privacy FAQs
Gemstone Articles
Royal Purple GarnetMadeira CitrineChrysoprase GemsVery Rare GrandidieriteRare Melo PearlsGuide to Green GemsMozambique RubyIolite GemstonesFancy Color TanzaniteColor Change DiasporeYellow or Golden BerylSpinel Gemstone PricesAn Exceptional 2.21 ct DemantoidType A Jade from BurmaCanary Yellow TourmalineRefractive Index ChartThai GemstonesRare GemsSapphire RingsAn Amazing Paraiba TourmalineRough and Cut GemstonesUmbalite GarnetRaspberry Rhodolite GarnetEmerald EnhancementsA Perfect 4 ct Tsavorite GarnetFluorite Gems and MineralsA Rare Vivid Mandarin GarnetRare SerendibiteDanburite GemsTrillion Cut GemsBurma Sanctions on Ruby & JadeRare Red Imperial TopazTourmaline Gems for SaleHigh and Low ZirconsSpinel JewelryBlue ApatiteCut and Polished GemsAmetrine from BolivaRare JeremejevitePrecision CutGemstone PhotosAustralian GemsLoose gemstonesSize and WeightBuying Gems in BangkokTop Grade GemsEngagement RingsHistory of BirthstonesPrice per CaratAfrica GemsAfrican AmethystCitrine QuartzCats Eye GemsPink GemstonesMadagascar SapphirePlatinum Jewelry
Customer Reviews
Beautiful Kunzite Pendant
Hello Ron, the Kunzite pendant arrived already today. It is very beautiful! Thank you very much. You will hear from me again:) Take care,
-- YEH, USA, Oct 2020
Tanzanite ring is perfect, excellent product and first rate service
Hi Ron, the ring arrived and is perfect. It is on her hand. The cut, polish, color and clarity of the Tanzanite is superb as far as I'm concerned. Thank you and all at AJS for providing this excellent product and first rate service. Sincerely,
-- TD, USA, Oct 2020
Santa Maria Aquamarines are stunningly beautiful
Hi Ron: The 4.54 ct Santa Maria Aquamarines are stunningly beautiful. To hold them in the light is almost indescribable, like the worlds best sapphires  THANK YOU.
-- RS, Canada, Sep 2020
Citrine Pendant is stunning!
My 9.18 ct Citrine pendant is stunning!! Thank you, again!! Everything I have ever bought from AJS is gorgeous!!
-- CJ, USA, Sep 2020
Beautiful stone, thanks for your excellent service
Hi Ron, It's a beautiful stone [2.16 ct unheated Blue Sapphire] - thanks for your excellent service. As Arnie says..."I'll be back."
-- SP, USA, Aug 2020
Read more Reviews ...
Payment | Shipping | Privacy policy | Return policy
